evelive.com 2016-06-23

# 

At Pinnacle Secure Services Inc, respecting your privacy is important to us. Pinnacle Secure Services Inc is committed to ensuring your privacy, in accordance with the provisions of United States law regarding the protection of privacy when processing personal information. 

When the user visits or signs up for the Pinnacle Secure Services Inc Website, the user sends Pinnacle Secure Services Inc personal information that can refer to, but not be limited to: 

  * \- information regarding the visitor's identity: name, address, and other contact information such as telephone number, email address, user name, password, and IP address
  * \- financial information such as information regarding credit cards
  * \- communications data

  1. ## Data processing goals

By submitting their personal information, the Website user thereby grants explicit permission to process said personal information for the following purposes:

    * \- facilitating the use of webcam services provided by third parties
    * \- offering you payment options for the use of said webcam services
    * \- sending you information bulletins, SMS
    * \- automatically generating user profiles
    * \- optimizing management of the Website and the services offered
  2. ## Direct marketing

We may also use said data for direct marketing purposes. You have the right to contest said use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, by sending an email to the address listed below.

  3. ## Reporting problems

We also collect personal information when you send us an email to report a problem. By doing this, you thereby expressly and unambiguously authorize the processing of said personal information by us. We use the information collected this way only to solve the problem reported or to send you a response.

  4. ## Information bulletin

When you sign up, you may receive information on webcams, new features, offers, and services by email. These emails will be sent by Pinnacle Secure Services Inc, 616 North Flores St., Apt. 101, CA 90048 West Hollywood, United States - Telephone No.: +352 2088 0401 – [support@dnxnetwork.lu](mailto:support@dnxnetwork.lu). If you do not wish to receive this information, go to the "My Account" section, visible at the bottom of every page. 

  5. ## Data protection and security measures

We take into account appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against occasional or unauthorized destruction, accidental loss, changes or access in order to ensure that the personal data of the Website user will not be damaged, destroyed or exposed to third parties and in order to prevent unauthorized access by third parties.

  6. ## Saving communications information

If you choose to use the chat room or other interactive communications options, you thereby accept this information being stored. Pinnacle Secure Services Inc will save said information based on need in order to resolve disputes, provide assistance, and research problems as the law allows. Pinnacle Secure Services Inc will not share this information with third parties except in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials in the context of a criminal investigation or suspected illicit activity. 

  7. ## Third parties

We will never not sell or transfer said information to third parties. The information you provide us can be transferred to Pinnacle Secure Services Inc partners in order to offer you webcam services. 

  8. ## Cookies

When you visit our Website, information may be saved by us on your computer in the form of a cookie. This cookie lets us improve the quality of our services and make your next visit to our site as easy as possible. Most web browsers let you delete said cookies from your hard drive, block them, or be informed of their presence. For more information regarding these functions, please read the instructions on your browser's information screen.

  9. ## Access right

You always have the right to view your personal information and have it modified free of charge when it is no longer up to date. The simplest way is to send a written request to [support@dnxnetwork.lu](mailto:support@dnxnetwork.lu). 

  10. ## Additional Information

If you would like more information, do not hesitate to contact us by email to [support@dnxnetwork.lu](mailto:support@dnxnetwork.lu) or by writing to Pinnacle Secure Services Inc - 616 North Flores St., Apt. 101, CA 90048 West Hollywood, United States. 

These privacy protection rules were last modified on 12/14/2011. Pinnacle Secure Services Inc reserves the right to modify these regulations regarding privacy protection at any time, pursuant to all applicable laws and regulations.
